coder.com 2019-04-25

# Coder - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains how Coder Technologies Inc. ("Coder", "we", or "us") collects, uses, and discloses information we obtain through www.coder.com (the "Website") and our related websites, networks, applications, mobile applications, and other services operated by Coder that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively with the Website, the "Service").

This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into Coder’s Terms of Service (the "Terms"). Any terms not otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy will have the meanings set forth in the Terms. By [agreeing to this Privacy Policy in your account setup, or by] using the Service, you consent to the processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

How We Collect your Information

##### Information You Provide

We collect any information that you provide us when you use the Service.

##### Registration and Profile Information:

When you register for the Service, we will ask you for your name, email address, mobile phone number, and billing address. We may also collect your information from a supported third party website when you use your credentials from those sites to log onto the Service. For example, when you log in with your GitHub credentials we may collect the information you have made publicly available on that service, such as your name and username. We may also obtain other non-public information from these supported third party websites with your permission.

##### User Inputted Code:

We collect the code you submit to our Service in order to provide you cloud based development tools and services.

##### Payments:

If you make payments through the Service, we will ask you to provide your payment information, such as your credit card number and billing address, so our service providers can process your payment.

##### Communications and Other Interactions:

We may collect information you provide when you communicate with our customer-support team.

##### Information We Collect When You Use Our Service:

We may automatically collect certain technical information from your computer or mobile device when you use the Service.

##### Device Information:

We receive information from your device, including IP address, web browser type, mobile operating system version (to the extent applicable), and unique device identifiers. We may also collect and store your browser settings and preferences.

##### Usage Information:

We receive information about your interactions with our Service, such as your interactions with the Website, the time spent interacting with features, and the dates and times of your visits.

##### Information from Cookies and Similar Technologies:

We and our service providers may collect information using cookies or similar technologies. Cookies are pieces of information that are stored by your browser on the hard drive or memory of your computer or other Internet access device. Cookies may enable us to personalize your experience on the Service, maintain a persistent session, passively collect demographic information about your computer, and monitor other activities. Our Service may use different kinds of cookies and other types of local storage (such as browser-based or plugin-based local storage).

How We Use Your Information

##### Service-Related Usage:

We use the information we collect about and from you for a number of purposes, including: providing, supporting, and improving our cloud based development tools, analyzing how you use the Service, managing our network, and better tailoring content and features.

##### Communications:

We use your information to communicate with you. For example, we may send email to the email address you provide to us to verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, or system maintenance. In addition, text messages may be sent to support two-factor authentication or notify you of important account security events.

##### Marketing:

We may use information we collect for marketing purposes, such as providing you with promotional materials that may be useful, relevant, valuable or otherwise of interest to you. Where required under applicable law, we will obtain your prior opt-in consent to send you electronic marketing communications.

##### Compliance with applicable law and our own obligations:

We may also process the information we collect about you or from you for the following purposes: (i) to enforce our Terms or other legal rights, including intellectual property infringement; (ii) as may be required by applicable laws and regulations or requested by any judicial process or governmental agency; and (iii) comply with industry standards and our policies.

##### Aggregate Data:

We may de-identify your information and process it in an anonymous and/or aggregated form for other purposes than described above.

How We May Disclose Your Information

##### Service Providers:

We may share your information among our vendors, service providers, and other third parties that perform services on our behalf. In addition, we may use third party analytics vendors to evaluate and provide us with information about your use of the Service. We do not share your information with these third parties, but theses analytics service providers may set and access their own cookies, pixel tags and similar technologies on the Service and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you which they may collect over time and across different websites. On the Website, we use Google Analytics to collect and process certain analytics data; Google provides some additional privacy options described at www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners.

As Required by Law and Similar Disclosures: We may disclose information about you: (i) if we are required to do so by law, regulation, or legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; (ii) in response to requests by government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities; (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect against or respond to physical, financial or other harm, injury, or loss to property; or (iv) in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual unlawful activity.

##### Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers:

We reserve the right to transfer your information to service providers, advisors, potential transactional partners, or other third parties in connection with the consideration, negotiation, or completion of a corporate transaction in which we are acquired by or merged with another company or we sell, liquidate, or transfer all or a portion of our assets. We may also disclose your information with your permission. In addition, we may share anonymous and/or aggregated reports and information on user demographics and traffic patterns with third parties.

Your Choices And Rights

If you do not want the Service to collect information through the use of cookies, your browser may allow you to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and restrict or disable certain cookies. Each browser is different, so you should check your browser’s "Help" menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Please be aware that if you disable or reject cookies, some features and Service may not work properly. You can opt-out of receiving further promotional messages from us by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional email you receive or by contacting us directly at the contact information listed below.

How We Hold and Protect Your Information

We maintain administrative, technical, and physical safeguards designed to protect the information you provide or we collect against accidental, unlawful, or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure, or use. Unfortunately, the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us. Moreover, we are not responsible for the security of information you transmit to the Service over networks that we do not control, including the Internet and wireless networks.

Children's Privacy

The Service is not intended for children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect information online from children under the age of 13. If Coder becomes aware that any person submitting information to the Service is under the age of 13, we will promptly take steps to delete or anonymize any personal information and terminate the user account. If you become aware that your child or any child under your care has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at the contact information listed below.

International Users

If you are visiting from the European Economic Area or other regions with laws governing data collection and use, please note that we may transfer your information to recipients in countries other than the country in which the information was originally collected, including the United States of America. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy. By providing your information and/or using the Service you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Changes To Our Privacy Policy and Practices

This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our information practices or relevant laws. To inform you of any change, we will post the updated Privacy Policy on the Website and indicate at the top of the Privacy Policy when it was updated. If we decide to use particular personal information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will let you know through our Services, by email, or other communication.

How To Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, our privacy practices or if you would like to exercise your rights and choices, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by writing to us at:

Coder Technologies Inc.  
ATTN: Legal Department  
4901 E. Cesar Chavez Street  
Austin, TX 78702
